<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gallery</string>
    <string name="storage_permission">Storage Permission</string>

    <string name="storage_permission_msg">
        Hello there! To ensure that our app works smoothly, we need your permission to access your device\'s storage. Can you please grant us permission to read storage?
    </string>

    <string name="rate_us_msg">
        Thanks for using our app! If you\'ve had a positive experience with it, please consider leaving us a 5-star rating in the app store. Your feedback helps us improve and reach more people. Thanks again for your support!
    </string>

    <string name="feedback_mail_subject">Feedback of %1$s</string>

    <string name="about_us_desc">
       Discover your photos like never before with our offline gallery app. Our app provides you with a seamless and enjoyable photo browsing experience, even when you\'re not connected to the internet. We\'re committed to providing you with a user-friendly and customizable platform to help you store, organize, and relive your favorite moments. Thanks for choosing our app and we hope you enjoy using it!
    </string>

    <string name="feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="rate_us">Rate Us</string>
    <string name="spread_the_word">Spread the word</string>
    <string name="spread_the_word_summery">
        Sharing is caring! If you\'re enjoying our app, why not spread the love and share it with your family and friends? Our offline gallery app is the perfect tool for anyone who loves photography and wants to keep their favorite photos organized and accessible, even without an internet connection. By sharing our app with your loved ones, you\'ll be giving them the gift of easy photo browsing and management. So go ahead, share our app today and help us spread the joy of photography!
    </string>

    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="app_version">App Version</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="appearance">Appearance</string>

    <string name="feedback_desc">
       We hope you\'re enjoying our app! Your opinion matters to us, and we\'d love to hear your thoughts on how we can make it even better. If you have a moment, please leave us some feedback in the app store. Your feedback will help us continue to improve our app and provide the best experience possible. Thank you for your support!
    </string>

    <string name = "coming_soon">Coming Soon</string>
    <string name = "coming_soon_msg">
        We\'re sorry, this feature is not available yet. We\'re working hard to add it in a future
        update. Thank you for your patience and understanding.
    </string>
</resources>